SEBASTIAN ŚLEDŹ

WFB DFSIGNER & DEVELOPER

Location Warsaw, Poland

Contact

sebastian@sledz.xyz +48 510 843 906

https://sledz.xyz



ABOUT ME

I specialize in web design and front-end development. I really like the clean design and having fun with new technologies. I am an infinite learner, tester, writer. I got into JavaScript frameworks with Vue.js as a framework of choice. It seems fun. Besides that, I also did a demo or two with Laravel. I work mainly in VS Code but as I don't limit my interests I have a good knowledge of Adobe CS, Figma, JIRA, Confluence and a variety of apps that prove helpful during creations. I have more than 6 years of freelance experience as a designer/developer and about 3 years of full-time contract in the remote company. This just proves my ability to stay in line with daily remote routine - calls, standups, commitment, and contribution. I have experience working in agile teams. I believe good design is within a grasp, for this reason, I like to think beyond colors and layout to consider the motivations of users.



WORK EXPERIENCE

GREEN HERRING STUDIO

Web Designer and Developer, 2012-current

Here begins my freelance experience as a Web Designer and Developer. For fun, as a volunteer or for commercial clients I prepared a variety of works from posters and illustrations, through animations and flash banners, to responsive websites and some branding designs.

FLEX FUNDING

Web Designer and Developer, 2016-current

I am responsible for development of company website, branding materials for web and print, making graphics for advertising and social media. I work mostly with HTML/CSS, JS, PHP (WordPress) and in Adobe Creative Suite.

CITI INTERNATIONAL

Database Analyst , 2014-2016

I worked on object-relational databases and reporting with Visual Basic and SQL Reporting Services.



EDUCATION

WARSAW SCHOOL OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Warsaw, Poland 2015-2016 Web Database Applications

UNIVERSITY OF FINANCE AND MANAGEMENT

Warsaw, Poland 2004-2010 Psychology



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Prototyping	•	•	•	•	•	O	•	0	0
Graphic Design	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
GIT	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
Visual Studio	•	()	•	•	•	•	•	•	0
PHP	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
HTML&CSS	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	O	0
JavaScript	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0
SOL	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	\circ	\circ



PERSONAL SKILLS

Social Commitment	•	•	()	O	()	•	•	0	0
Organization	•	O	O	O	O	()	•	0	0
Creativity	O	()	()	()	()	()	•	()	•
Communication	\odot	()	()	()	O	()	0	0	\circ
Positive Attitude	•	•	•	O	O	()	•	•	•



LANGUAGES

Polish (native)	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•
English	•	•	•	•	•	•	O	0	0
Russian	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0



COURSES

IBM: MOBILE APPLICATION SPECIALIST

Warsaw, 2016

This course was a complete guide to mobile application development. I learned about programming with HTML5 and Dojo Mobile, ¡Query scripting or working with IBM Worklight.

MICROSOFT: PROGRAMMING WITH C#

Warsaw, 2015

This course provided a solid foundation in object-oriented programming knowledge. This was my introduction to the C# and the world of .NET which I continue on postgraduate studies.



HOBBIES AND ACTIVITIES



Bicycle riding



Coding



Photography



Travelling